Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1950-2007
George Mason University Libraries
- Arena Stage printed materials, 1950-2000; 53.5 linear ft. (107 boxes)
  - misc. large print programs (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - misc large print programs (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - misc. large print programs (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - misc. large print programs (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - braille perfomrance guide: Molly Sweeney (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Measure for Measure (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: The Subject was Sex: Too much and too little (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Bette and Boo (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Marat Sade (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Merrily We Roll Along (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: The Man who came to dinner (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: midsummers night dream (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: midsummers nights dream (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: misalliance (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Montieth and Rand (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Montieth and Rand (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Montieth and Rand (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: A Month in the Country (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Moonchildren (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Moon in the Yellow River (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Mother Courage (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Mr. Arcularis (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Mummenschanz (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: MyChildren! My Africa! (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: National Health (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: National Theatre of the Deaf (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Nevis Mountain Dew (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: 'night Mother (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: The 1940's Radio Hour (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Nightclub Cantata (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: No Place to be Somebody (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Nothing Sacred (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: OBA KOSO (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Old Times (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: On the Razzle (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Once in a Life Time (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Once in a Liftetime (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: One Flew over the Cuckoo's Nest (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The foursome (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: geniuses (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Gertrude Stein (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Gemini (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Flying Karamazov (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Flying K's (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: The Flying Karamozov Brothers (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Fool Show (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Front Page (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Galileo (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: An Enemy of the People (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Enrico IV (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: The Firebrands (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Enrico IV (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - press coveage: Epitaph for George Dillon (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Execution of Justice (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Fences (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Press coverage: The Autumn Garden (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Avner the eccentric (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Avner the Eccentric (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Awake and Sing (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Banjo Dancing (1 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Banjo dancing (2 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Banjo Dancing (3 of 3) (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Battle Dream (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Beckett Plays (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Beehive (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Beyond Therapy (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Billy Bishop goes to War (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: The Blood Knot (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Boccaccio (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Born Guilty (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Briar Patch Originals (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: The Brother Karamozov (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Buried Child (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The Burning of the Letters (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: The Cage (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: The Caine Mutiny Court Martial (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - press coverage: Candide (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - press coverage: Catsplay (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: The Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Caucasian Chalk Circle (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Cerceau (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Checkmates (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Chemmy Circle (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Cherry Orchard (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - The Cherry Orchard (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Press coverage: The Cherry Orchard (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: "The Child" and "Disability" (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Children of Darkness (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: A Chorus of Disapproval (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Clandestine (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Closer Than Ever (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Cloud 9 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: Cocoanuts (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Cold Storage (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Comedians (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: A Conflict of Interest (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Conquest of the South Pole (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Crime and Punishment (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: The Crucible (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Crucible (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Curse of the Starving (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Cymbeline (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Dance of Death (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Dandelion Wine (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Dark of the Moon (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Death of a Salesman (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: A Delectable Judge (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Delicate Balance (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Design for Living (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: The Devils Disciple (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: The Devils (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Disability (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Disenchanted (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: A Doll House (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Don Juan (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Duck Hunting (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Dybbuk (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: The Egg (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Emigres (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Emlyn Williams (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Enchanted Night and the Police (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Enemies (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - misc. press coverage: 1960-1961 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - misc. press coverage: 1982 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: The Resistible Rise of Arturo (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: As You Like It (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Ascent of Mt. Fuji (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: All the Way Home (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: American Buffalo (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: American Film (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: American Splendor (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: An American Tragedy (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Andersonville Trial (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Accidental Death of an Anarcist (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: The Adding Machine (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: The Affair (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: After the Fall (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Ah, Wilderness! (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Alice in Wonderland (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: All-American Repertory (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: All the King's Men (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Abyssinia (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - misc. press coverage: 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - misc press coverage: 1960-1964 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: 1975-1976 season (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: The Seagull (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Serjeant Musgrave's Dance (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: She Stoops to Conquer (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: She Stoops to Conquer (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Silent Night, Lonely Night (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Six Characters in Search of an Author (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Six Characters in Search of an Author (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Six Characters (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: "Sizwe Banzi is Dead" and "The Island" (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Skin of our Teeth (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: Stand-up Tragedy (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - press coverage: starting here, starting now (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Status Quo Vadis (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Edith Stein (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Still Life (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Stray Dogs (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Streamers (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: A Streetcar Named Desire (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Suicide (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: King Lear (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: The Taming of the Shrew (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Taming of the Shrew (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Tales from the Vienna Woods (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: Tartuffe (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Teibele and her Demon (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: The Tempest (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Tenth Man (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Thief (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Three Men on a Horse (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Three Men on a Horse (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Three One Acts (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Three Short Plays (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Three Sisters (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: The Three Penny Opera (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The Hollow (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Home (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Horatio (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: The Hostage (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Hotel Paradiso (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: The House of Blue Leaves (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: I am a Woman (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Iceman Cometh (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Idiot's Delight (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: invaild (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The Immigrant (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: The Importance of Being Earnest (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: The Importance of Being Earnest (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - press coverage: In Celebration (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - press coverage: In the Process (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - press coverage: Indians (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - press coverage: Inherit the Wind (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - press coverage: The Inspector General (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - press coverage: The Inspector General (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Isn't it Romantic (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Jacques Brel (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Come and Gone (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: Julius Caesar (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Julius Ceaser (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Kean (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: King Lear (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Ladder to the Moon (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: The lady's not for burning (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Juno and the Paycock (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The last meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Late Great Ladies (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Les Blancs (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: A lesson from Aloes (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: A lie of the Mind (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Leonce and Lena (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Light up the Sky (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: Little Theater ofthe Deaf (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Long Day's Journey into Night (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: A Look at hte Fifites (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: Look back in Anger (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: Loose Ends (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - press coverage: The Lower Depths (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: MacBeth (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - press coverage: Lonesome Train (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - press coverage: The Great White Hope (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Great White Hope (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - press coverage: Hamlet (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Happy End (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Hasty Heart (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Heartbreak House (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Heartbreak House (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: The Works of Beckett (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - press coverage: Madness Film (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - misc. press coverage: 1973-1974 season (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - press coverage: Madwoman of Chaillot (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - press coverage: The Magistrate (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - press coverage: Major Barbara (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - press coverage: Major Barbara (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - press coverage: major barbara (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - press coverage: Man and Superman (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - press coverage: Man and Superman (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - press coverage: The Man who cam to Dinner (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - press coverage: The man who came to dinner (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - misc. press coverage: 1968-1969 season (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - press coverage: The Marriage of Bette and Boo (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - press coverage: Measure for Measure (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - press coverage: Merrily We Roll Along (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - press coverage:brochure: audio described series 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - large print program for "Constant Star" (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - large print program for "Anthems:Culture Clash in the District" (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - large print program for "Ain't Misbehavin' (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - large print program for"Book of Days" (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - large print program for "An American Daughter" (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - large print program for "Theophilus North" (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - braille program for "An American Daughter" (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - braille program for "An American Daughter" (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - braille program for "Book of Days" (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - braille program for "Book of Days" (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - braille program for "Ain't Misbehavin" (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - braille program for "Aint misbehavin" (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - braille program "anthems:culture clash in the district" (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - braille program for "anthems:culture clash in the district" (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - braille program for "Theophilus' North" (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - braille program for "Thephilus' North" (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - braille program: South Pacific (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Polk County (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - development reports 1990 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - development: budget and reports 1987 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - "curtain" speeches for fund raising (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - congressional development (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Board meeting Feb. 1989 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Irving Berlin's Birthday Bash - 5/24/88 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - communiccations plan 1988 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Fall Conference 1981 / Aspen Institute (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - report on potential endownment campaign (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Development: staff recommendations and meeting minutes (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Trustee Training manuel 1981 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Israel trip (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Orkeny, Istvan visit 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - 30 year commemorative fund (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Trustee organization (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Congressman Wright's performance of "Ourselves Alone" (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - The Group (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Yuri Lyubimov visit (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Development Director search (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Russia Tour - 1989 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Congressman Wright farewell party: responses/ general info (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Congressman Wright Farewell party: Invitation list (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Wright party info (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - board retierment 1987 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - five year plans (misc. years) (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - board of trustee's retreat 11/9 - 11/11/1990 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - brochure: Share the Spotlight (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - interview: Mansbach 1-6-84 (cassette tape) (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - board retreat: 1983 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - elspeth udvarhelyi (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - telemark wky. Rep - Start up (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - press releases 1963 season (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - press releases 1964 season (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - press releases 1963-1964 season (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - press releases: 1964 season (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - press releases: 1965 season (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - press releases: 1965 season (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - press releases: 1966 season (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - press releases: 1968-1969 season (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - photos of Congressman Wright farewelll gala (Box 89)
    6 photos in binder box.
  - press clippings of 1987 - 1988 season (Box 90)
    3 large black photo binders
  - press clippings from 1988-1989 season (Box 91)
    5 large binders organized by months.
  - press clippings on 1972-1975 season and Russian tour (Box 92)
    5 large binders.
  - braille program: Mrs. Klein (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - braille program: School for Wives (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - braille program: The Visit (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Time of Your Life (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Trinidad (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Wonderful Life (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - braille program: Yerma (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - braille program: Before it Hits Home (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - braille program: Born Guilty (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - braille program: Caucasian (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - braille program: Cerceau (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - braille program: Closer Than Ever (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - braille program: My Children! My Africa! (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - braille program: Our Town (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - braille program: Stoops (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - braille program: Two Gentlemen of Verona (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - braille program: The Seagull (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - braille program: Way Home (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - braille program: African Company (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - braille program: A Small World (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Auner (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Brothers K (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Its the Truth (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Summer and Smoke (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - braille program: Of Thee I Sing (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - braille program: Way of the World (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - braille program: Jar The Floor (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - misc. braille programs: 1986-1987 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - misc. braille programs: 1989-1990 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - misc. braille programs: 1987-1988 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - misc. braile programs: 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - braille program: A Community Carol (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - braille program: A Month in the Country (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - braille program: A Perfect Ganesh (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Arcadia (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Butler (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Cat (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - braille program: Dancing at Lughnasa (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Dinah (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - brille program: Fires in the Mirror (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - brille program: Hedda Gabler (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - braille program: It Aint Nothin but the Blues (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - braille program: I am a Man (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Long Days Journey (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Misalliance (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - braille program: The Miser (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Molly Sweeny (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Six Characters (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Sons (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - braille program: The Plough and the Stars (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Twelfth Night (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Black no More (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Constant Star (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - braille program: coyote (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Dimly (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - braille program: george (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - braille program: ghosts (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Hope (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - braille program: House Arrest (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - braille program: K2 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - braille program: lovers (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - braille program: play on (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - braille program: pleasure (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - braille program: theatre staff as of 5-1-01 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Le Bon Cafe dinner menu (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Vanya (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Vanya (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - braille program: You Can't take it with you (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Ad Season brochure 00-01 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - braille program: A month in the Country (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Animal Crackers (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Blithe Spirit (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - braile program: blues for an Alabamer Sky (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Butler (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - braille program: Candide (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Women (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - braille program: Thunder (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - braille program: The Matchmaker (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - braille program: The Waiting Room (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - braille program: The Plough and the Stars (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - braille program: The Father (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - braille program: Oak and Ivy (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - braille program: How I learned to Drive (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - braille program: Holiday Heart (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - braille program: Dance of Death (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - braille progam: Coming of the Hurricane (Box 107, Folder 7)
- Arena Stage Photographs, 1950-1991; 18.75 linear ft. (15 boxes)
  Photographs of Arena Stage theater productions during from 1950 to 1991.
  - Abyssinia 1988 - 1989 (Folder 1, Box 1)
    Tina Fabrique, Norgen Crayton, Fanni Green, Kimberly Harris, LaDonna Mabry, Mary Bond Davis, David Toney, Rufus Bonds, Jr
  - The Accidental Death of an Anarchist 1983-1984 (Folder 2, Box 1)
    Richard Bauer, Raymond Serro, Tom Hewitt, Michael Seter, Susan Plaksin, Michael Jeter,
  - The Adding Machine 1951 (Folder 3, Box 1)
    Warner Shreiner, Jacqueline Dudley
  - The Affair 1964 (Folder 4, Box 1)
    George Ebeling, Bella Jarrett, Anthony Juke
  - After the Fall 1980 (Folder 5, Box 1)
    Linda Lee Johnson, Stanley Anderson, Joanne Hrkach, Inga Bunsch, Halo Wines, Maeve McGuire, Richard Bauer, Mark Hammer
  - Ah, Wilderness 1954 (Folder 6, Box 1)
    Gerry Hiken, Lady Astor
  - Ah Wilderness 1979 (Folder 7, Box 1)
    Mark Hammer, James Jenner, Barbara Sohmers, Robet Prosky, John Wiley, Annalee Jefferies, Joanne Hrkach
  - Alice in Wonderland 1950 (Folder 8, Box 1)
    Lester Rawlins, Marry Mangum, Henry Oliver, Dick O'Neill
  - All My Son's 1954 (Folder 9, Box 1)